LAYLA ALMARWANI

7783864374

Laylaalmarwani.top@gmail.com



AlmarwaniLa



Portfolio

SKIILS

React HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap and jQuery

Ruby on Rails, Node.js And Express

DATABASE Postgre-SQL

DEVELOPMENT & OPERATIONS

Git, Github, NPM Webpack, Hiroku and Netlify.

CODE EDITOR

Visual Studio

KNOWLEDGE

Python & C++

EDUCATION

Web Development BootCamp CodeCore College 2020 - 2021

Computer science Diploma TVTC, Saudi Arabia August 2014-May 2017

Training on Digital Marketing, TVTC, Saudi Arabia 2016

SUMMARY:

Jr Web Developer with experience working on several projects, passionate about solving problems and learning new technologies . Background working with non-profit organizations. I enjoy building games using Python and C++ in my free time.

PROJECTS:

THE SOCIAL HOME- ONLINE MARKETPLACE.

Front End: ReactJS | Back End: Node.JS | Database - CMS

- A fast filtering and search experiences.
- Contact form to receive submissions using EmilJs.
- Updating and managing data quickly with CMS.

E-COMMERCE - ONLINE STORE

Front-End :THTML5, CSS3, React | Back-End: Redux, Node & Express | Database : MongoDB .

- Users are able to create accounts.
- Users are able to search by filtering items.
- User are able to use payment method.
- Users are able to order items and leave reviews.

LET'S CHAT- REAL TIME MESSENGER.

Front End: ReactJS | Back End: Node.JS - Socket.io

- Real time messaging experience.
- Ability to create your own community rooms.
- User able to use emojis.

CHESS - MULTIPLAYER CHESS GAME.

Front End: CSS & HTML | Back End: Python

- Users able to play realtime chess.
- The application generates multiple rounds.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Accor Bullman Zamzam Hotel, Medina SA

Guest Relations - Data Management - August 2017 - November 2017

- Record quality incidents based on customer feedback
- Develop periodic quality analytics on guest experience
- Maintain record of monthly quality trends and drive quality improvement initiatives in lagging departments

ISSofBC, Burnaby BC

Volunteer Interpreter/Administrative Assistant - March 2018 - April 2018

- Simultaneous in person translation of Arabic to English and vice versa to assist refugees and asylum seekers in settlement in Canada
- Ensure that the clients and volunteers understood each other.
- Entered client tax data into IRCC database.
- Answered phone calls. Organized meetings for supervisor and team members.

Frog Hollow Neighbourhood House, Vancouver CA

Youth worker- September 2018 - March 2020

- Provide social, recreational, and skill development activities for youth.
- Provide a physically and emotionally safe environment for all program participants, staff, and
- volunteers.
- Simultaneous in person translation of Arabic to English and vice versa
- Create and implement a plan to provide support to vulnerable youth.
- Leading youth and advocate for them.
- provide 1-1 settlement support to youth as required.
- Ensure programming fits within approved budgets.